Contact

jamesonyemi@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/james-yemi (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

JavaScript PHP MySQL

Certifications

PHP Tutorial Course SQL Fundamentals course JavaScript Tutorial

james yemi

Web Application Programmer at Essien Arthur Computing Ltd. Dome

Summary

Experienced Web Application Programmer with a demonstrated history of working in the information technology and services industry. Skilled in PHP, Laravel, JavaScript, AdonisJs, JQuery, MYSQL, MARIA-DB and Business Development Strategies etc. Strong engineering professional with a Diploma focused in Software Engineering from Advanced Information Technology Institute (Kofi-Anna Centre of Excellence).

He currently applied for a Computer Science, an online Program (afour-year period) at the University of the people and uses other selfpaced platforms like OSSU to learn about CS.

Experience

Essien Arthur Computing Ltd. Web Application Programmer January 2020 - Present (8 months) Greater Accra, Ghana

Africaloop Limited
Backend Developer (PHP)
October 2016 - September 2018 (2 years)

#8 Swaniker Road Abelenkpe, Accra - Ghana P. O. Box KD 1373, Kanda

Education

Advanced Information Technology Institute (Kofi-Anna Centre of Excellence)

Diploma, Software Engineering · (2016 - 2016)